{
    "subject": "resource/Don't_Raise_the_Bridge,_Lower_the_River",
    "predicate": "ontology/editing",
    "object": "resource/Bill_Lenny",
    "human_readable": "Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River was edited by Bill Lenny.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9638373255729675,
            "question": "Who edited the book 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8867925405502319,
            "question": "Who might have contributed to 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.844846785068512,
            "question": "What is the significance of the title 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7969685196876526,
            "question": "What type of work might 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773095428943634,
            "question": "Where might you find a book like 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.703834056854248,
            "question": "What kind of audience would enjoy reading 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4821246266365051,
            "question": "What is the title of the book edited by Bill Lenny?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4395259618759155,
            "question": "Can you name a book edited by Bill Lenny?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4247185289859772,
            "question": "Is Bill Lenny known for editing books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05295991897583008,
            "question": "What are some common themes in books about rivers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River was edited by Bill Lenny.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3651_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bill Lenny known for editing books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3651_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a book edited by Bill Lenny?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3651_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the book edited by Bill Lenny?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3651_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3651_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"editor: Bill Lenny;\" for the film \"Don\u2019t Raise the Bridge, Lower the River,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided to contradict the statement about Bill Lenny being the editor of \"Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River\", but there are many other pieces of information that do not mention editing at all.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}